One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Doflamingo Arrives!
The Ultimate Schemer!
Backtracking in time a bit
30 minutes before Caesar's exchange
Dressrosa
Everybody is naked before my eyes.
I've seen everything that's been in your mind since we first met.
I've heard that you have a soft spot for women,
but I didn't expect it to be this soft.
How pathetic.
Your collar is all wrinkled and your tie is crooked.
Your shirt is stained with blood.
You look terrible.
You're a good-for-nothing man, "Black Foot" Sanji!
Did you really think that a guy like you could win my heart?
Donquixote Family (Trébol Army)
Assassin: Violet
That's hilarious.
I can't believe you were fooled by Sis' beauty, you stupid jerk!
You're lying, Violet-chan...
Hey, quit dreaming! Sis was just acting!
I-I know you have a beautiful heart...
Why are you still saying that after getting hurt so badly?
Hey, stand up!
You must have been coaxed into this by some bad guys.
You don't even want to be here.
Violet-chan...
Why don't you quit being so romantic?!
So stupid!
That's terrible! But she's beautiful!
That was a hell of a kick, Sis!
You're trying to hold back your anger
against me while looking for a way to escape.
Did you think you could trick me with your lies?
Lies don't work on me.
I ate the Glare Fruit and became an insight human.
I can see through anything.
Men are all liars.
I'll let myself see what's in your head full of lies.
Why did Trafalgar Law and Straw Hat become allies?
What are your goals, both on Green Bit and on Dressrosa?
What's your plan and what are you up to?!
You don't have to tell me.
All the answers are inside your head.
We will catch all of your crewmates.
It's coming! That pose!
Peeping Mind!
W-W-What's the matter?!
Sis!
H-How perverted!
Perverted?!
I've never seen such an erotic mind!
What?!
What about your plan?! Your true purpose?!
What are you thinking under these circumstances?!
I'm thinking about you.
The way you looked at me at that moment...
I want you to kill someone!
I knew you were telling the truth!
It doesn't matter if a million people denounce you...
I'm not going to doubt a woman's tears!
What a stupid thing to say...
What a dumbass!
Sis, if this pervert is useless to us now, let's kill him and get it over with!
A 77 million bounty!
A member of the Straw Hat Crew! The head of "Black Foot" Sanji!
Let's collect!
Hierro Lagrima!
Iron Tear
Whoa! Sis, what're you doing?!
Eye Whale!
Violet-chan, you really were working for Doflamingo against your will, weren't you?!
Run, Black Foot.
Violet-chan, what about you?!
Forget about me!
Why?!
We know what you people have been doing all along.
I was your enemy but you kept believing in me!
You really are a good-for-nothing man!
Thank you for your concern back there.
It made me so happy!
I don't know the situation, but you don't want to work for Doflamingo, do you?!
You even fought your own men!
Let's escape from this island together on our ship!
Look at me, Black Foot!
From the moment you all arrived here with Caesar,
you were walking into that man's trap!
Trap?
Look inside my head.
What you see is Dressrosa this morning.
Your Majesty!
Don't say you quit!
Doflamingo-sama!
Please explain!
Why did you abdicate from the throne?!
How noisy. Aren't they here yet?
What?!
A warship is arriving at the harbor!
I've seen that logo before!
Cipher Pol Aegis Zero!
They're the Government officials who work directly under the World Nobles!
Why are they here?
Remain calm, citizens of Dressrosa.
Regarding the report on Doflamingo's abdication from the throne and the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
that spread all over the world...
It was a mistake. Just a false report.
And, the news of this will spread around the world in the extra edition, today at 3 in the afternoon.
It's going to be a secret until then.
You mustn't tell anybody about it.
All citizens should keep living peacefully as if nothing has happened.
What's with this cunning deceit that seems plotted by a fox?!
The World Government?!
It's beyond a Warlord's control, isn't it?!
I'm...
scared of Doflamingo so I can't run away, but maybe you people can get away in time!
Present time
Green Bit
What should I do?!
Wow! What's this? Nico Robin's upper half popped out!
Nico-ya!
I was listening to the conversation. It was Sanji, wasn't it?
Hey, where are your real body and Nose-ya?
If what Black Foot-ya was talking about is true, the deal with Doflamingo is off.
Huh, off?!
Then, what's gonna happen to my hand-over?!
Nico-ya! Summon Nose-ya!
Let's get off of the island now!
The thing is, we're under Green Bit right now!
Under?!
We had some trouble...
But both Usopp and I are safe.
We can't help you, but if you're gonna escape, go without us.
We'll go to the harbor where we agreed to meet up.
Okay, understo-
T-The Navy!
He's here.
Good luck!
You guys, too!
Joker!
Hey, Law!
You've done well, all things considered!
I didn't expect to see a Navy Admiral here!
Since I'm no longer a Warlord, I'm scared as hell!
Liar!
At the same time in Dressrosa
"Corrida Colosseum"
Now, all the competitors of
Block C are finally in the arena!
Fighter
Gladiator
139 warriors!
Assassin
Bounty Hunter
Fighter
It's a battle royale!
Boxer
Who's gonna win this?!
Bullfighting
Former Pirate
Giant Warrior
Assassin
Finally!
Now, the battle is...
You're already in the ring? Straw Hat!
You're in Block D, aren't you, Cavendish?!
Are you trying to break in?!
Let go of me!
Cut it out! Or you'll be eliminated!
Let's do it!
Simultaneously
All around the world
An extra edition?!
It seems like a correction about something.
What the hell is this?!
I'm a Candidate for
Warlord of the Sea
The big news about Doflamingo was...
Incorrect?!
That's insane!
Green Bit
You used the authority of the World Government.
You fooled the whole world... only to deceive ten of us?!
Usually, the more spectacular the magic show, the simpler the trick behind it.
Law.
"There is no way he would do such a ridiculous thing."
People usually have a preconceived idea
or an assumption, which leaves a blind spot.
You're a pirate!
Even if you're a Warlord of the Sea and a king,
you don't have the power to spread a lie all over the world!
The only people in this world who have the power to do such a ridiculous thing are...
the Celestial Dragons!
You don't know about Joker's past.
And that will cost you your life!
Don't tell me... you're...
It's bit more complicated.
Law.
Anyway...
I've been wanting to kill you!
Joker! Kick this guy's ass alrea-
There is no way I'm gonna hand him over!
You didn't follow any of my terms!
Doflamingo! This deal is off!
No! W-What're you talking about, you fool?! We got this far!
Is that how you talk to your boss after 10 years of silence?
Leave him, Law.
Caesar is one of my precious subordinates.
Jo...
Issho-san, it's Caesar Clown who is with Law.
I see. He is the scientist from the poison gas incident...
Joker!
But if he is that Warlord's subordinate, he won't be charged.
They'll grant him amnesty.
It's you!
You are Fujitora, appointed as a Navy admiral by the World Military Draft.
I've heard about you.
They say you and Ryokugyu are insanely powerful monsters, with unquestionable power.
Ryokugyu: Green Bull
Oh, why thank you.
Don't play dumb.
I'm still new to the Navy so it's hard for me to understand what you're doing.
I don't have enough evidence yet, but I have received information about you breaking the rules as a Warlord.
The man right there was calling you "Joker"; is that your nickname?
If you want to investigate me, you have to be really determined and collect enough evidence.
Now, what's the Navy's decision about Law's punishment?
Regarding the news about you and the wanted pirates, the Straw Hats,
if you have formed an alliance as reported in the news, you're guilty!
If they have become your subordinates, Law-san, you're...
not guilty!
Our mission depends on your response.
We may have to arrest you and the Straw Hats.
H-Hey, what kind of decision is that?! He can just get away by lying!
Our original plan is ruined.
Now we're being targeted.
Even if I take this matter to Dressrosa,
the situation will only worsen.
I need to buy some time.
The Straw Hats are not working under me! It's an alliance as the article states!
You're such a clumsy man!
Then, we have to strip you of your title.
It'd be if the news ended here, but...
You're kidding me...
A meteorite!?
I-It can't be!
Hey, stop joking around!
Run!
A meteorite is falling on us!
A-Amazing.
W-Where's Issho-san?
What?! What just happened?!
Only the three spots that they're standing on are untouched!
How did the Fleet Admiral train you?! You damn stray dog!
It doesn't matter if he can see or not.
Oh, thank you. I simply wanted to test your skills.
"Dressrosa"
Team Franky
The Flower Field?! Are you gonna go on a picnic?!
Speaking of picnics, where did you wonder off to, Sanji?!
I've been...
in love!
Oh, that's nice to hear. By the way, I think I can find the factory.
Really?!
But unfortunately, we can't just destroy it and get away.
It's gonna be a much bigger task than we expected.
Hey, wait! We don't allow credit!
Somebody, catch that toy!
He ran away without paying!
We don't have time! Doflamingo was...
Yeah, I just read the extra edition. He sure fooled us!
If he gets Caesar back, our entire plan ends in failure!
Let's destroy the factory and put his nose out of joint!
Anyway, come meet us at the Flower Field!
I'm asking you what's with that fairytale-ish place?!
By the way, I can't reach Nami-san!
You still think she's a weakling? She's gonna be fine!
Brook and Monster Chopper are with her!
What is that?
Huh? What's wrong?
Violet-chan, what is that?
That's a broadcast from the Colosseum.
The unknown gladiator, Lucy, is pretty strong!
He's small but tough!
Franky, you won't believe this but, Luffy is...
Yeah, he's fighting in a competition now.
Why did you let him?!
You should've kept an eye on him!
You're in no place to judge me!
Black Foot, I have to go!
My men are coming after me!
You want to go to the secret factory, don't you?
Here is a map.
It's disguised as "Toy House."
But that's the factory.
Hey, I can't take this!
If you help me more, you're gonna...
You're a funny man. It doesn't make any difference.
It seems like the executives already know that I betrayed them.
Violet-chan...
The western harbor! Meet me there!
Hide yourself there and wait until I get there!
That's our rendezvous point!
I will help you get away from here at any price!
You really are a good-for-nothing.
Sorry to interrupt, you good-for-nothing!
You fool! Where did you come from?!
Oh, Violet-chan?!
You have to beat them all up first.
There he is!
A-Amazing!
Why didn't you do it yourself?
I couldn't do anything because they're holding Kanjuro as a hostage.
You have to come with me, Sanji-dono! To the place called Toy House!
That's where they are keeping my fellow samurai, Kanjuro!
I don't know where it is, though!
Back on "Green Bit"
Beneath the forest
Tontatta Kingdom
What's causing the ground to shake?
It must be Law and the others.
Damn! I don't wanna die here!
What?!
The hero is getting upset!
J-Just kidding. The truth is the shake was...
caused by my Haki.
Haki?! Isn't that the technique that you used to beat 50,000 villains on Fishman Island?!
As expected from our hero!
Your energy can shake up this kingdom!
Please, please eat this!
It's a Fighting Fish. It's big and a close relative of the goldfish.
A Fighting Fish?!
Yes!
It's good! I didn't expect it to taste this good!
It tastes like the sea monster that I killed.
As I thought,
they're the ones who caught the Fighting Fish.
What kind of strength is that?
The Dwarf tribe is super strong, isn't it?
They're pretty big so they can provide food for the kingdom for months.
Usoland, you're a Big Human so I guess you can eat a lot.
Luffyland who belongs to my fighting force, the Usolanders,
can eat the whole fish with one bite!
What's an Usoland?
Look. Doesn't that look familiar?
He's from the picture book that we read in Jaya.
Is that a statue of Montblanc Noland?!
Yes, it is!
You know him too, don't you?
He was a Big Human botanist who came to visit this kingdom 400 years ago.
At that time, villainous Big Humans were devastating the island.
Seeing that our ancestors were troubled,
he fought alongside us and led them to victory.
He became the legendary hero of the Tontatta Kingdom!
When Usoland said his name and told us that he's one of his descendants,
I was speechless!
L-Look at my head!
This chestnut-shaped head is the proof!
It's true!
The chestnut-shaped head!
I didn't have any idea! I'm so sorry!
You're a horrible person.
You were saved by it too!
Let's eat, get some gifts and go!
This must be destiny.
To see them today.
Indeed!
Today is the day we vowed to fight Doflamingo...
and after 400 years, a legendary hero has came along again!
Usoland! After you finish eating, let's go to the Flower Field via the underground passage!
Let's go!
Yeah!
In Dressrosa, where we're gonna fight,
the commander and our fellow soldiers of King Riku's Army are expecting us!
Yeah!
Please stand at the forefront and lead us!
Let's destroy the Donquixote Family!
Yeah!
With Usoland, we're unbeatable!
Our hero!
Usoland!
Translation & initial timing, Tsuki, Yibis (Opening)
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Halee
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, Crunchyroll